Welcome back to City TV with Wembley awaiting for Manchester City.
They prepare to face Arsenal in the 2026 Carabao Cup final.
It is the Blues' fifth appearance in the showpiece event in the space of 10 years under Pep Guardiola, who has described reaching the final as an honour.
City booked their place at Wembley with a comprehensive 5-1 aggregate victory over Holders Newcastle United in the semi-finals whilst Arsenal overcame Crystal Palace to set up one of the most eagerly awaited Cup finals in recent memory.
The two sides sitting in first and second place in the league last met in a League Cup final in 2018 when Guardiola claimed his first piece of silverware at the club courtesy of a convincing 3-0 victory.
Arsenal, who have been runners up in this competition a record six times, will be desperate to not extend that record and instead lift the trophy for a third time in their history.
City's recent record against the Gunners makes for fascinating reading.
Guardiola's side have not beaten Arsenal in any of their last six meetings, a run stretching back to the famous 4-1 triumph during the treble-winning campaign of 2022-2023.
But Pep Guardiola has plenty of form in this competition and winning today will put him clear as the manager with the most League Cup wins in English football history.
We shall see if Pep can earn himself yet another record shortly.
But first of all, let's preview the game with all of the team news, build-up and pre-match interviews from Wembley Stadium.
Aguero will find his way through here, Sergio Aguero with the lobo of the goalkeeper, sits here in front in the Caribbean Cup final.
Ahead of this showpiece match, we look back at the last 10 goals scored in League Cup finals by Manchester City, starting with Yaya Toure's Thunderbolt against Sunderland in 2014.
It's an astonishing equalizer.
Well, it's going to be a terrific turning point.
It is!
From Stamford Nursery!
Five against two.
To wrap up the Capital One Cup.
Now that's the pass.
Here he comes.
Hazel's now ass.
It's Manchester City Trophy.
They break the length of the Wembley pitch to get the third crucial goal.
Finish off Brave Sunderland.
Aguero, beautifully brought down by him.
Wait for Fernandino, who scored?
The deadlock is broken, it's Fernandino with the goal.
Aguero, he'll find his way through here, Sergio Aguero with the lobby of the goalkeeper, sits here in front, in the Caribbean Cup final.
Sergio Aguero, fight for it.
Blue shirts waiting the box.
I've never thought about taking that short.
This one is making its way.
Crosby finds his way in Vincent Coppany scores the captain's goal in the Carabao Cup final Abby Silver Silver turns and he mastered the ball now to make it 3-0 Struck by Aguero is the opening goal of the Carabao Cup finals scored by Sergio Aguero The penalty spot is headed in by Rodrigo.
That's two for Manchester City.
Andrew is headed into the net.
I'm Rickland Portis scored for City.
And perhaps it is enough for the cup.
The manager spoke to the press in the build-up to the match.
Pep Guardiola confirmed that James Trafford would starting goal for the final, continuing as the designated Cup goalkeeper after impressing in both legs of the semi-final against Newcastle.
Josco Guardiol remains sidelined with a broken leg and will play no part at Wembley.
Mark Gaye is ineligible for the contest, having arrived after the competition cut off.
Joining them on the sidelines is Huben Diage, who suffered an injury in the Champions League game against Real Madrid.
In total, there are four changes from that side made by Pep Guardiola in a very attacking lineup.
That gets us up to date with the team news.
So let's head over to the mix zone now where the cameras are waiting to pick up the pre-match interviews.
Bernardo, you've played finals, you've played big matches, won trophies with this club, but how do you see this team in terms of maturity to play a final?
It's a good question.
We'll see.
It's a final, as you said.
It's a very important game.
First trophy there.
We can win this season and we're looking forward to it.
There's been a lot of talk about City having the experience to win this trophy and having experience to win trophies, but how does this effectively come into play in a final?
Is it better game management or more calmness?
Each game is a different game.
I do believe that both teams are prepared to play this final.
We hope it goes our way today and hopefully it's going to be a very good day for us.
We've seen this fixture have different looks, so how do you imagine the fact that you guys are facing each other in a final to reflect on the type of game that we'll have today?
I would say that it doesn't count that.
A final is always a final.
It doesn't really matter the form that the teams are in, I think, in a final because...
because it's a game of emotions, it's a game of little details, so we'll see what happens.
How can you capitalize on the urgency that Arsenal has by not winning a trophy for so long?
Well, that's not something that we can control.
We can control our own performance, and the only thing that we have to do is be ready, perform as best as we can, and win the title.
Four managers stand together tied for the record of four League Cup victories.
Alex Ferguson, Brian Cloth, José Mourinho, and Pep Guardiola.
Victory today will put Pep out on his own with a new record five cup wins.
I don't allow them to forget anything we have done.
We have done it in the past.
Who is there?
Why shouldn't we do it now?
This is the motto, this is the challenge.
Expecting a big battle here in North London, his Arsenal against Magic.
It's a massive, massive game.
We had to be ready.
Marmooch grinders and Marmooch comes forward.
A real chance for Marmooch.
I think we're forgetting the most important thing.
We're forgetting about focusing just on ourselves.
Show ourselves out there how much we want to win it again.
We have to take responsibility.
You have to fulfill it.
Otherwise, for nothing.
We're going to do it to the end.
To the end.
Keep on doing, keep on doing, keep on doing.
This is the kind of game that they find a way out of to win.
Now it's time to hand over to the match as Manchester City take on Arsenal in the 2026 Carabao Cup final.